orojackson.com 2017-01-15

# Privacy Policy | Oro Jackson

**BY REGISTERING ON ORO JACKSON, YOU AGREE TO HAVE READ AND ACCEPTED THE PRIVACY POLICY MENTIONED ON THIS PAGE AND AGREE TO HAVE READ OUR[COMMUNITY GUIDELINES](http://orojackson.com/pages/rules/).**

## PRIVACY

This policy covers how Oro Jackson treats personal information that Oro Jackson collects and receives in connection with your use of the Oro Jackson website and related products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

Oro Jackson may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes. 

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND ITS USAGE

While registering on Oro Jackson, we ask you for the following details; 

  * **Name** : This is a publicly visible username that is displayed along with content you share on Oro Jackson.
  * **Email** : We ask you to provide us with an Email ID to verify your account and contact you. This information is **never made public** and **is never shared** with any third party.
  * **Password** : Your password is only known to you and isn't available to anyone else.
  * **Date Of Birth** : You are given the option to control who views your date of birth, however Oro Jackson **Administration (Admins)** can view your date of birth regardless of your privacy settings.
  * **Gender** : We ask you to provide your gender which is publicly visible to everyone.
  * **Time Zone** : We ask you to provide your Time Zone so that you may view all time stamps in your local time. This information is only available to you and Oro Jackson **Administration (Admins)**.

Additionally, after registration you have the capability of sharing other information about you in connection with your access to and use of the site, such as contact information, location, etc. Do note that such information is **visible** to all members and guests (depending on your profile privacy options). To know how to control your profile privacy please read the [frequently asked questions](http://orojackson.com/pages/faq/). In addition to the information you provide, Oro Jackson automatically receives and collects information such as; 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

We use the above information we are provided with to further improve your experience on Oro Jackson. We also make use of **Google Analytics** to learn about visitors and their behavior on Oro Jackson. No personally identifying data is included in this type of reporting. Such information is never made public or shared with others. You can opt out of sharing data with Google Analytics, to learn more [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

IP addresses of computers used to visit Oro Jackson are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question. **Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time and is not shared with anyone**. 

It's also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) by posting on the publicly visible parts of the community (such as threads, profile pages etc.), that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the sharing of any personally identifying information on the publicly visible parts of the community. 

### INFORMATION YOU SHARE WITH ORO JACKSON ADMINISTRATION

There are instances where we ask you for personal information such as your **address** , **phone number** and **full name**. This information is asked **only when** you participate in events (such as a manga giveaway) where we need to ship the winning prize/gift to you. This information will **only be asked by Divvens or Freeze** (Oro Jackson Administrators).

The information you provide is also shared with the courier service that we use to send you the prize/gift. If you are unsure about sharing such information, kindly do not participate in such events. 

**Oro Jackson is not responsible if you share such personally identifiable information with other users apart from Divvens or Freeze.** Oro Jackson does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you. Orojackson.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Oro Jackson. 

Oro Jackson has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and Oro Jackson cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. 

### COOKIES

Cookies are small files stored on your computer by your web browser (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox) at the request of a site you're viewing. This allows the site you're viewing to remember things about you, such as your preferences and history or keeping you logged in. Cookies may be stored on your computer for a short time (such as only while your browser is open) or for an extended period of time, even years. Cookies not set by this site will not be accessible to us.

**Our Cookie Usage**  
This site uses cookies for numerous things, including: 

  * Registration and maintaining your preferences. This includes ensuring that you can stay logged in and keeping the site in the language or appearance that you requested.
  * Analytics. This allows us to get determine how people are using the site and improve it.
  * Other third-party cookies for things like Facebook or Twitter sharing. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them.
  * Advertising cookies (third-party). Cookies may be set by the advertisers to determine who has viewed an ad or similar things. These cookies are set by third parties, in which case this site has no ability to read or write these cookies. For further information kindly read "Advertising Partners" section below.

Controlling cookies and cookie preferences must be handled within your browser. Here is a list of guides on how to do this for popular browser software: 

### ADVERTISING PARTNERS

http://orojackson.com may display advertisements from Google AdSense, an advertising service provided by Google. It makes use of the [DoubleClick](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090) cookie, when users visit http://orojackson.com and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). To learn more about Google Adsense, [click here](https://support.google.com/adsense/troubleshooter/1631343?hl=en). You may also opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

Published:
    Jul 12, 2011
Page Views:
    13,491
